Contact

39 Rissik Street, Johannesburg 065 891 6831 (Mobile) lungileprince@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/prince-mangwa-5a928174 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Conflict Management
Personal Loans
Communication

Honors-Awards
Certificate Of Participation.

Prince Mangwa

2nd Year Student at WeThinkCode_.
Johannesburg Metropolitan Area

Summary

About:

Full Stack Software Developer in training with more than 5 years experience in finance for both public and private sector.

Passionate about technology and its continuous growth.

An individual who is always looking for an opportunity to learn, teach and implement. Goal driven completing the now preparing for next.

I enjoy working in a team as i get to learn more and contribute to self growth while contributing to the task at hand.

Experience

Capitec Bank
Sales Consultant
April 2015 - February 2016 (11 months)
Jane furse

General sales and customer services

Mpumalanga Department of Health State Accountant 2012 - July 2013 (1 year) Mpumalanga, South Africa

Pep Stores Merchandiser September 2012 - October 2012 (2 months) South Africa

packing shoes and clothing on shop floor

Education

WeThinkCode

Computer Software Engineering · (2021 - 2023)

sekhukhune fet college

financial management, Finance and Financial Management Services · (2010 - 2012)